export const quizData = [
    {
        question: "What comes next in this sequence: 2, 6, 12, 20, ?",
        option1: "30",
        option2: "32",
        option3: "34",
        option4: "36",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "If a train travels 60 miles in 1 hour, how long will it take to travel 180 miles at the same speed?",
        option1: "1 hour",
        option2: "2 hours",
        option3: "3 hours",
        option4: "4 hours",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which number is the odd one out: 5, 9, 15, 21, 27?",
        option1: "5",
        option2: "9",
        option3: "15",
        option4: "27",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the missing number in this pattern: 3, 6, 9, 12, ?, 18?",
        option1: "13",
        option2: "14",
        option3: "15",
        option4: "16",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "If you rearrange the letters 'CIFAHR', you would get the name of a:",
        option1: "Country",
        option2: "Animal",
        option3: "City",
        option4: "Fruit",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following numbers is the next in the sequence: 1, 4, 9, 16, ?",
        option1: "20",
        option2: "24",
        option3: "25",
        option4: "30",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "A clock shows the time as 3:15. What is the angle between the hour and minute hands?",
        option1: "30 degrees",
        option2: "0 degrees",
        option3: "60 degrees",
        option4: "90 degrees",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "If five cats can catch five mice in five minutes, how many cats are needed to catch 100 mice in 100 minutes?",
        option1: "10",
        option2: "20",
        option3: "50",
        option4: "100",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which word does not belong with the others: Cucumber, Carrot, Broccoli, Spinach?",
        option1: "Cucumber",
        option2: "Carrot",
        option3: "Broccoli",
        option4: "Spinach",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "In a group of 15 people, 10 are wearing glasses. What percentage of the group is wearing glasses?",
        option1: "50%",
        option2: "60%",
        option3: "70%",
        option4: "80%",
        ans: 4
    },
];
